Oh, thank goodness. Stay, Mrs. Butterworth.
Stay, damn you! Stay! Stay! Stay!
真见鬼，站着别动，Butterworth女士，操！，别动！
Good morning, Mrs. Jefferson.
早安啊，Jefferson
How are you? Oh. Oh! How are
you? Oh, you're shaking.
你好吗？你在发抖
Thank you for coming.
谢谢你能过来
Okay
好的
Thank you for coming.
谢谢你能过来
Oh, that's all right.
没关系啦
On your day off especially.
尤其是在这特殊的一天
Oh, come on. Are you kidding me?
Where is it, out back?
别开玩笑了，在哪呢，在里面？
It's in the trap.
在陷阱里
In the where?
哪？
In the trap.
在陷阱里
Okay. All right, it's okay.
好了
Thank you for coming on your day
off.
I got our little friend.
我认识了一些人
Is it ugly?
丑吗？
Is it ugly? They're all
beautiful to me.
丑?他们都美极端了
Kept us up all night long with its ruckus.
Didn't it, Mrs. Butterworth?
吵了整整一个晚上，是吗，Butterworth女士
Butterworthless when it comes
to catching critters.
At 5:06 A.M. I heard that trap shut,
and I called you ASAP. You're on my speed dial.
凌晨5点06分的时候那个陷阱在响，我马上呼叫了你
I know, Ann.
我知道，Ann
I hope you rot in hell, you
filthy vermin!
我诅咒你在地狱里腐烂，肮脏的寄生虫
Okay, I'm going to set it loose
in the park, okay?
好了，我准备在公园里放了他，好吗？
Yeah, set it loose in the park.
好的
Break his neck first.
拗断他的脖子
Alex? Alex-
Yeah.
I am... I'm just... I'm so
embarrassed.
我，我只是，很困扰
The darned government was late with my Social
Security check again, so I brought you this.
没用的政府又没有签我的社保，所以我只能给你这个了
Oh.
A little sugar.
一点糖
That is so sweet of you. Thank
you.
你真好，谢谢
It's full of maraschino cherries,
and I left off the stems this time.
一杯满满的酒浸樱桃，这次有茎哦
Wow. Well, you can never count
on the government for anything,
知道了吧，永远别相信政府
but you can always count on me.
My favorite client.
但你能永远相信我，亲爱的顾客
You are such a nice guy.
你真是一个好人
Ah, well...
好吧
How come...
为什么
...a nice guy like you is still
single?
你这么优秀却还是单身呢？
I ask myself that same question every day.
I guess I just haven't met the right girl yet
这个问题我思考了很久，最后的答案就是还没遇见合适的女孩
When you do...
你什么时候..
...she's going to be exhausted.
她一定累坏了
That was awkward. Okay, bye,
Mrs. J. I'll see-
太辶,拜,J女士,明天..
Alex, Alex.
Yeah.
是
You have a spider on your arm.
你胳膊上有只蜘蛛
What? Oh, that's a tattoo.
什么?噢,那是纹身
A spider. No, no, no, no. A
spider is on your arm.
是蜘蛛,不,有只蜘蛛在你胳膊上
Oh, look at that. Look at that.
Oh, that's a brown recluse.
看呀,看着,是只褐皮花蛛
This is highly poisonous. As long as you don't provoke it,
so we just have to stay calm. Okay?
这蜘蛛的很毒的,所以我们要冷静,别激怒它,好吗?
Let me help you.
我会帮你的
Remain calm, okay?
不要慌,知道吗？
Let me help you. I can-
我来帮你，我可以-
No, no, stay calm means I don't
need your help.
不，保持冷静的话我就不需要你的帮助了
Okay, let me help you.
好了，让我来帮你
No, don't help me. You just stay
calm. No, Mrs. J. No-
不，别过来，你才保持冷静，不，J女士，不-
Paging Dr. Bender. Paging Dr.
Bender.
呼叫Bender医生，呼叫Bender医生
Was that a dead body?
那是个尸体吗？
Let's not focus on that,
Mister...
别盯着那个，小姐
Mathis. Was that one of your
patients, Nurse...
Mathis，那是你的病人吗，护士...
Lisa? I mean, I-I don't care.
I'm not saying that you were responsible for that,
Lisa?我是说,我不管,我不认为你要对这个负责
but being your next patient I
was just a little concerned.
但是作为你的下一个病人我有点小怕
You know, I would imagine, if I
looked up the word "nurse" in,
你知道,我会想象,如果我在护士日志,
let's say,
Nurse Journal or Nurse Illustrated or whatever it is,
或者护士说明书还是说明的查找护士的定义的话
that I would probably see a
picture of you.
可能那说的就是你
I mean, you are, like, the
perfect nurse.
我的意思是,你是,就像一个完美护士
Are you done?
说完了吗?
Okay.
恩
Okay, so it says here you have a small
puncture wound on your upper arm.
你的胳膊上面有一个伤口对吗
Correct.
是的
Can you remove your shirt,
please?
你能脱掉你的上衣吗
Sure.
当然了
It might be a bullet wound,
though, actually,
可能是枪伤,实际上
because I'm dodging bullets all
day long in what I do.
因为我整天都在躲子弹
And what is it that you do?
那你是做什么的?
Um, well, I actually-
好吧,我实际上-
Ow, ow. I, uh... Actually, I
shouldn't tell you. It's top secret. Ow.
噢,实际上我不能告诉你,最高机密
I'd say you're a comedian, but the shirt
gives you away. So do your work books
我不得不说你有喜剧天分,但你的衣服和你的工作薄出卖了你
Well, Mr. Mathis, it looks like one of your bugs bit you.
From the swelling, I'd say a spider.
Mathis先生,似乎是你的虫子咬了你,看伤口的肿胀,应该是蜘蛛
You know what? You'd be right.
It was a brown recluse.
被你发现了?是的,是只褐皮花蛛
All right,
let's just do 1/10 cc of Dexamethasone or cortisone,
好了,只需要给你注射0.1毫升的氟美松(抗炎药)或者可的松(肾上腺素)就行了
whatever you want. It's not my
first barbecue.
请便,反正不是我第一次被咬了
Okay, let me check that with the doctor.
I'll be giving you these shots myself.
好的,我去跟医生说一声,待会由我来给你注射
Then you'll be out fighting
bugs again in no time.
很快就会好的
Uh, nurse... Lisa... let's say for
a second that this is lethal,
呃,护士,Lisa，这是个致命伤
and, you know, I've only got
one meal left.
你知道的，我只剩下一餐饭了
What do you say, you, me,
breakfast? Huh?
你说什么,你，我，还是早餐？
No.
不
It's too early for this crap and
need some help from the captain.
现在还太早了，我们需要总部的帮助
Jeez.
老天
$200 for gauze? Seriously, I
hope they accept fruitcake as
200美元的纱布？我希望他们接受用
payment because I don't know
what I'm going to do.
水果蛋糕来支付，因为我不知道怎么办了
Okay, everybody calm down. It's
just a fire alarm.
大家别激动，只是个火警
Walk out, please. Slowly. Let's go, sir.
Don't worry. Don't be scared.
走出来，慢慢的，别担心，别害怕
It's okay, don't run. Slowly,
slowly.
好了，别跑，慢一点，慢一点
Okay, it's fine, folks.
没事了，大家
It's fine. Everything's fine.
好了，所有人的没事
Ladies and gentlemen, may I have
your attention, please.
女士们先生们，请注意一下
Uh, this is a false alarm. It
is a false one, folks.
警报误响了，是个误会
There's no fire in the
building,
大楼里没有火宅
so if we could all just remain
calm, that would be great.
所以我们都冷静下来，这样很好
Jose, I need you to turn the
damn thing off.
Jose，去把该死的警报关了
Okay, you got it, boss.
听你的，老板
Thank you.
谢谢
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
You know what? I can help them out if you want.
You want me to help them out?
你知道吗？如果你需要我就能帮他们出来，你想我去帮他们出来吗
No, we're okay. We're fine.
不，我们没事，我们很好
You sure?
你确定？
Yeah, we got it.
是的，我们能搞定
Excuse me, Director?
打扰一下，导演？
Yes.
是的
Carl has something very crazy to
say.
Carl要说一个很疯狂的事
There's something in the morgue.
陈尸所里有东西
It climbed right out of a body bag,
and it bit me. I swear to Christ.
它从尸体袋里爬出来咬了我一口，我发誓
Like the... Like the living dead,
Carl?
像，像活死人一样，Carl？
Jose, please.
别这样，Jose
Sorry, I like those movies.
我喜欢这些电影，不好意思
Carl, what the hell are you talking about?
Did you pull the fire alarm again?
Carl，你他妈在说什么？你又拉响警报了？
Hell, yes. Didn't you hear what I said?
There's some sort of animal that's down here.
对啊，你没听见我说什么吗？有什么生物在下面
Okay, but, Carl, you work at a hospital.
If something bites you,
好了，但是，Carl，你在医院里，如果有什么东西咬了你
there's doctors and nurses
everywhere.
这里到处都是医生和护士
There's no reason for you to pull a fire
alarm and alert the entire building.
你不能就这样拉响警报惊动整个医院
But it bit me, boss. It bit me.
它咬了我，老板，它咬了我
Maybe somebody brought in a dog.
可能谁带了狗进来
It's not a dog. Listen, I know how this sounds,
but you should have seen it.
不是狗，听着，我知道那种声音，你们应该见过
It's got these long black legs, like a spider,
but it's much too big to be a spider.
有长长的黑腿，像蜘蛛，但是比蜘蛛大多了
We've got to call somebody.
我们要找人了
Look, if it was bigger than a
spider, it wasn't a spider.
听着，如果比蜘蛛大很多，那就不是蜘蛛了
I'm sure-
我确定
A black cat, maybe, Carl.
大概是指黑猫，Carl
It's too big to be a-
那太大了对于-
Call somebody
喊人
Was it a monkey?
是猴子吗?
Why would it be a monkey?
怎么会是猴子呢？
Could've been a spider. Carl,
right? Okay. Listen,
也许就是蜘蛛，Carl，好吗，听着
it may in fact have been a
giant tarantula.
可能是一只巨型狼蛛
I've seen tarantulas as big as
a foot across.
我见过跟脚一样大的狼蛛
Who's this guy?
这家伙是谁？
He happens to be an
exterminator.
他像终结者
Spiders happen to be my
specialty.
我是来终结蜘蛛的
I know what spiders are thinking.
I get into a spider's head.
我知道蜘蛛在想什么，我知道蜘蛛的脑子是什么样的
I think like a spider. I move
like a spider, all eight legs.
我像蜘蛛一样思考，像蜘蛛一样行动，像有八条腿一样
I become a spider to catch a
spider.
我成了一名蜘蛛终结者
Okay, all right. Do you want to go down
with Carl and maybe take care of this thing?
你们想跟Carl一起下去，然后见见那个东西吗？
I'd really appreciate it. As you can see,
I've got my hands full here.
我很想去，但如你所见我忙着呢
Right now? Yeah.
现在？好
I'd really appreciate it.
我赞成
I would love to do that for you.
Carl, we could do that. Sure. I love to work pro bono.
我愿意为你，Carl，我们可以做的，我喜欢无偿工作
Okay, that's great. I appreciate
that.
很好，我很欣赏这个
No problem at all.
没问题
No problem. I just have a quick
thing to discuss. See this?
好的，我要问你下你们，看到这个了吗？
This is my bill for the hospital.
I haven't settled this yet,
只是的医院账单，到现在都没搞定
so I'll take care of this for you
if you take care of this for me.
所以如果你帮我的话我也会帮你
Sort of quid pro quo pro bono.
这是公平交易
Sounds fair to me, boss.
听起来很合理，老板
Thank you, Jose.
谢谢，Jose
Yes, fine. That's great.
Consider your visit on the house.
好的，很好，考虑到你来了
Thank you.
谢谢
Great. Okay, Carl, will you take this gentleman
downstairs, and let's get rid of this bug, okay?
很好了，Carl，你能带着这位好朋友下楼，然后除掉虫子，好吗？
Okay, boss, but I don't feel so
good.
好的老板，但我觉得不舒服
Let me see the bite.
让我看下伤口
Okay, I'm going to get you to
the E.R.
好的，我要带你去急症室
It's going to be an intern's
nightmare.
这将是实习生的噩梦
Woof.
Jose.
Yeah.
是的
Will you please take our bug-
killing friend to the morgue?
你能把被虫子要死的朋友带去陈尸所里去吗？
Oh, sure.
噢，好的
Anything he needs, just take
care of it, okay?
照顾好他，好吗
You got it, boss.
没问题，老板
Gracias.
谢谢
I'm going to have to grab a couple things from my...
from my truck.
我要从我的卡车上带些东西
That's okay.
好的
You're not a real police
officer, are you?
你不是警察吧？
Security guard.
保安
Okay. All right, my truck's out
back.
好了，我的卡车在后面
Okay. Oh, and they hand me a
gun.
噢，他们给了我一把枪
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
put it away.
拿开他
I will. I have handcuffs, too.
好的，我还有手铐
Good. Okay.
很好
I got some mace.
我有一些棒子
Sure.
当然了
So you get in the mind of the
spider, really?
你知道蜘蛛在想什么，真的吗？
I do
真的
That's crazy.
你疯了
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's a little
nuts.
是的，我是有点小疯
Sir, we have a location. E.T.A.
5 minutes.
长官，我们还有五分钟到达目的
It's over here.
结束
Uh-oh, the lights don't work so
good.
灯有些问题
It's cold in here.
这里好冷
No, spiders don't like it cold.
They like it warm. Dark and warm.
不，蜘蛛不喜欢冷，他们喜欢温暖，阴暗和温暖
Well, that's good.
好吧，这很好
Hey, Jorge.
嘿，Jorge
Uh-huh.
啊哈
Can you get my flash light? It's
in the side of my bag.
能递给我手电吗？在我包的侧面
Sure.
当然
My name's Jose. Okay? Okay.
我是Jose，OK？
Oh, my God.
我的天
What?
怎么了
Oh, God.
我的天
What?
怎么了
This is so gross.
太讨厌了
Oh, yeah? What?
为什么？
Look at this.
看这个
No, describe it. I'm not going
to look.
不，说给我听就行了，我不想看
Oh, uh.
What?
什么？
The spider must've... oh, he must've got inside
this guy's body and dug his way out through
蜘蛛一定，一定进入了这个家伙的身体里然后
his lungs or his stomach or
something.
从他的肺还是胃什么的挖了出来
What?
什么？
Oh, my God.
老天
Oh, poor guy.
可怜的家伙
How big did Carl say this thing
was? What did he say exactly?
Carl说那个东西有多大？具体点？
Exactly?
具体？
Yeah.
是的
Let me see. Uh, "He bit me, boss. He bit me."
And then Lisa said "It was a doggie.
我想想，噢，“他咬了我，老板，他咬了我，然后lisa说：是只狗宝宝
"He said, "No." And then I said,
"Maybe it was a black cat." He said, "No."
他说，不，然后我说，可能是只黑猫，他又说，不
"Then it's a monkey." He said, "No."
He said it was like a spider but bigger than a spide-
那就是只猴子，他还是说不，他说是指比蜘蛛大很多的蜘蛛
Maybe it was a spider monkey.
所以大概是只猴子蜘蛛
A spider monkey?
猴子蜘蛛？
A spider monkey.
猴子蜘蛛
Ooh, what is all this?
We already called. It was a false alarm.
这都是些什么？我们已经说了，是误报
No, it wasn't.
不，不是的
Is that, like, Raid?
那是，袭击吗？
Raid? No. Raid is for housewives.
This is a very potent brew,
家庭主妇才会招到袭击，这是个非常大的阴谋
my own concoction of sticky acid.
A few drops on a termite hive, and it's history.
我的粘性酸混合物曾
And it's eco friendly.
非常环保
Oh, that's nice.
很好
Okay, if you were a spider,
where would you be?
好了，如果你是蜘蛛，你会去哪
Oh, damn it.
草拟大爷你的
What?
什么？
Yes, I know, but I thought it was,
you know, spider... you were scared, too. Shut up.
我知道，但我以为那是，蜘蛛，你也被吓到了， -闭嘴
Where's this vent go to?
通风口通向哪的？
Uh, through the building, from the roof,
all the way down to the basement machine room.
穿过大楼，从房顶知道地下机房
The machine room?
机房？
Yeah.
是的
Where it's warm.
那里很温暖
Ah.
啊
Okay, Jose, get up there.
好了，Jose，起来
I'm not going to get up there.
我不会去那的
Come on, man. You're a little
guy. Get in the vent.
你是个小男人了，进通风管
I'm not going in there.
我不会去那的
I'm kidding. Get my bag for me.
开玩笑的，把包给我
It's not funny, man. But, listen,
are you really going to go up there?
这不好笑，伙计，但是听着，你真的要去那？
Yeah, that's what I do.
我就准备这样做
This is how I roll, man. There
is no bug that can outdo the Ex.
我是这样想的，宏基，没有虫子可以超越之前的
And besides, the bug that we're
dealing with?
更何况我们要面对的是？
Mm-hm.
Is a big bug.
是个大虫子
Ah.
In my line of work,
it's the little bugs you've got to be scared of.
在我这行里，都是一些你会害怕的小虫子
Oh, the little ones.
噢，小虫子
Yeah.
是的
Oh, I hate little bugs. You know?
I hate gnats, mosquitoes, cucarachas of course.
我讨厌小虫子，你知道吗？我讨厌蠓虫，讨厌蚊子，当然还有墨西哥舞蹈
I don't even like lady bugs.
You know, everybody likes lady bugs.
甚至瓢虫我都讨厌，你知道的，所有人都喜欢瓢虫
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的是的
I hate roly pollies, too. I
can't stand them. Chiggers:
我也讨厌圆滚滚的东西，不能忍受，恙螨
chiggers are, like, really bad
because they get under the skin.
恙螨真的很讨厌，因为他们喜欢钻到皮肤下面
Okay. Sorry, the one we're
looking for has a mean bite.
不好意思，我们找的
You've got a lot of elderly,
sick people, kids. Let's do this for the kids.
你已经找到很多老病人了，孩子，让我们为了孩子做这些
Let's do it for the kids.
为了孩子们
All right.
好了
I'll be on channel two. I'm going to need you
to talk me through the entire vent, okay?
我会在第二频道，我需要你通过整个通风管跟我说话，好吗
All the way through the building.
Wanna make sure this thing doesn't double back
所有通过大楼的路 想确定这个东西不会再从这些地方
and come back through this way.
走过了
Uh, wait a minute. I don't have
the sticky acid.
等一下，我没有粘性酸
Yeah, but you've got the gun,
you've got the handcuffs, the mace.
但你有枪，你有手铐，还有锤子
Trust me,
this thing is more scared of you than you are of it.
相信我，那东西会更加怕你一些
Huh, I don't think so.
我不这样想
Uh, sir, there are no cell phones in the hospital.
There's a sign right there.
长官，医院里没有电话 -那里有个标志
Set up a perimeter around the hospital.
Lieutenant, lock it down.
封锁医院 -封锁他，中尉
Uh, that is a negative, my friend.
Repeat, not happening. We have patients-
拒绝，朋友，我重复，这不可能，我们有病人...
Your hospital is now under my
command.
你的医院现在由我接管
I'm sorry. I'm Gordon Harris,
director of the hospital. Who are you?
不好意思,我是医院的总管Gordon Harris,你是谁?
I am Major Braxton C.
Tanner, Special Forces, United States Army.
我是Braxton C少校,美国特种部队
We have reason to suspect you've inadvertently
received a very dangerous contagion.
我们有证据显示你们受到了危险性传染
There's a body that was mistakenly
sent here to this hospital.
有具尸体被错误的送进了医院
We'd like to see that body.
我们要看那个尸体
A contagion?
传染性?
Now, where's the morgue?
陈尸所在哪?
Breaker, breaker,
this is the Ex calling El Dorado. Come in, Jose.
Ex呼叫El Dorado，请回答，Jose
Uh, hi, yes, I'm here. El
Dorado, did you say?
我在这，El Dorado,你说什么?
Yeah, El Dorado. I'm coming up to a junction,
east and west. Which way to the basement?
好的El Dorad，我在一个分支口，去地下室是向东还是向西，
Uh, what's a junction?
什么分支口？
It's uh... like when two roads come are...
you know, come together in a T,
就是，就像两条路，你知道的，像一个T字形
and you don't... Do I go left or
right to go to the basement?
你竟然不知道..我应该走左边还是右边？
Go left.
左边
What?
是吗？
Yes.
是的
Hello.
你在吗
Don't yell at me. Go left.
别对我喊，走左边
Left, right?
左，是吗？
Yes, go left, izquierda.
是的
Am I scared of what?
我在怕什么？
Go left.
走左边
Okay, I'm going left.
好了，我要走左边了
Jose, I'm not alone in here,
buddy.
Jose，我不是一个人，兄弟
Oh, my God.
老天
Jose. Jose, you're not going to
believe this.
Jose，你不会相信这个的
It looks like our friend has
already had a little snack.
看来我们的朋友已经吃过点心了
This is unbelievable and so beautiful.
The structure's incredible, the strength.
这太不可思议，太美丽了，精致的架构，还有力量感
I can't... I've never seen
anything like it.
我从没见过这样的东西
Oh, it's so sticky.
哦，而且非常黏
It's so sticky.
太黏了
Oh, good God.
老天
Oh, that's not good. That's not
good.
老天这可不好!
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no.
不
Come on.
来吧
Oh, that was interesting. Oh,
man.
这真有趣，伙计
So this is where the body
would've come in.
这就是尸体进来的地方吗
Our morgue attendant Carl's
fallen ill, so he-
我们的陈尸所人员Carl生病了，所以他..
Fallen ill?
生病了?
It is here.
在这
Move to full lock up, people.
All units gear up.
全面封锁,全副武装
So you're saying that the military can
just come in and shut a hospital down?
你是说你的部队可以进医院然后随便开枪?
That's not legal. You can't do
that.
这不合法,你不能这样做
The hell I can't. You are under military
jurisdiction on a matter of national security.
谁说不行,你在国家安全的军事管辖权范围内
Your full cooperation and discretion
would be very much appreciated.
您完全的合作和决定会受到表扬的
Do we have an understanding?
明白了吗?
Yep.
是的
Good.
很好
Excuse me, Director Harris?
打扰一下,Harris总管
Uh, not now, Lisa.
现在不行，Lisa
Can we talk for a second?
我们能聊一下吗？
Not now.
现在不行
Something's happened. It's one
of the patients.
有事发生了，是我们的以为病人
And?
然后呢？
Well, he's...
好吧，他
Dead?
死了？
Let's take a look.
我们看一下
Ah, okay. I'm onto you, buddy.
我知道你，伙计
It's already hunting.
准备好狩猎了
Granted the patient's immobility
indicates an advantageous access,
like a buzzard selecting wounded prey.
It will get the hang of the kill quickly.
How long has it been?
过去多久了？
Blood coagulation fresh.
Ten, maybe twelve minutes. It is close.
血液凝固刚凝固 -十或者十二分钟，差不多
How big do you think it is now,
Doctor?
现在多大了，你觉得呢？医生？
It has quadrupled in size.
已经四倍了
Qua... in 24 hours?
四..就一天内?
It will continue to grow exponentially.
Four hours from now it will quadruple again.
他会继续爆炸性增长,从现在开始四小时后又会长大四倍
Where are you, friend?
你在哪,朋友
Where are you, buddy? Come on, buddy.
The Ex has a treat for you. I got a... a treat for you.
你在哪,回答我,兄弟 Ex可以治疗你，我，我可以治好你
U.S. to Mexico.
U.S. to Mexico. Jose, it's Alex.
美国呼叫墨西哥，Jose，是Alex
Copy that.
收到
I think I found our spider. I'm down in the
basement, buddy. Down in the basement.
我发现我们的蜘蛛了，我到地下室了，兄弟，在地下室
Okay.
好的
Where are-
在哪..
There you are, little buddy.
Wow, you're not such a... such a little guy, are you.
到了，小家伙，哇，你是多么的..多可爱的小东西
All right, I've got something
for you.
我为你准备了些东西
I got something for you. Nice and shiny.
You're going to like this. Ready?
我为你准备了些东西,锃油瓦亮的,你要这样进去了,准备好?
That's my quarter. Give me back
my quarter!
那是我的给我!
Oh, no you don't. Not this time.
不行,这次不行
You gonna run from me?
你想从我这跑走?
Ah, come on, buddy.
来吧伙计
Get down!
趴下!
What, are you trying to kill me?
Hey, they said I could be here. What are you-
什么,你想要杀了我? 他们说我可以来这的,你是..
Hi.
嗨
Was that the only one?
那是唯一的一只吗?
The only what? Spider? Uh, yeah,
I hope so.
唯一的?蜘蛛?但愿如此
Shh-shh-
嘘
What?
怎么了?
Oh, great, it's gone.
好了,他走了
Yeah, nice job, moron.
是的,干得好,弱智
Made visual contact.
视觉解除
Moron?
弱智？
Target it now in the sewer
system. Prepare to move out.
锁定在污水管道系统，准备行动
Moron?
弱智？
I'm bringing an eye witness in
for questioning.
我带了一个目击证人在这
Hey, I had this thing bagged
until you started shooting at me.
No.
不
Shooting at me.
射我
Okay, you've got no idea what
you're dealing with
好吧，你不知道你要面对的是什么
Uh, excuse me.
不好意思
Sorry. Sorry.
对不起
I'm a professional.
我是一个教授
Oh, I see. I see. Of course you
are. And, hey, nice uniform.
我知道，你当然是，不错的制服
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
Now, move out.
现在，行动
That was sarcastic.
这真讽刺
Move out.
走
Are you feeling something?
'Cause-
你感觉到什么吗？ 因为
Head out.
出发
Stuck.
Did you ever see the arachnid?
你有见过八脚怪物吗？
I don't know what that is. Did
you say Iraq?
我不知道你在说什么，是伊拉克吗？
Arachnid.
八脚怪物
I like your pipe.
我喜欢你的管子
Major, here he is, a local
exterminator. Uh, Alex.
上校他在这，当地的驱虫人
Alex Mathis, actually. It's pest
eradication specialist.
Alex Mathis，实际上是杀虫专家
All kinds of pests, rodents,
reptiles.
所有的害虫，啮齿动物还是爬行动物
All I want from you, Mr. Mathis, is details.
Tell me what you saw down there.
我想从你那知道的，Mathis先生，只有细节，告诉我你在下面看到了什么
Hey, there he is.
他在这
Hey, how you doing?
嘿，你好啊
What's up, Jose?
怎么了，Jose？
In concise sentences, please.
说简单点，请
Okay, can I sit down? It's been
one hell of a morning.
我能坐在这吗？已经过了一个早上了
Yeah, we're going to sit down,
okay?
是的，我们准备坐下，好吗？
You want details? This thing's
huge.
你想要细节？这可是个大事
This is the biggest spider that I've ever seen,
maybe the biggest spider on record,
这是我见过最大的蜘蛛，可能是世上最大的一只
and from the look of the bite
that it gave that mortician,
从它给入殓师造成的咬痕来看
I'd say this thing is highly
poisonous, aggressive, fast, smart.
我的说这家伙非常的毒，而且充满了进攻性，快，聪明
It's strong, really strong.
It moved that sewer grate out of the way.
非常的厉害，它从下水道里走了出去
That's got to be about 25 pounds.
This is a big-ass spider.
大概有25磅重，是个恶魔蜘蛛
Exoskeleton's hardened then.
It's already entered Stage Two.
先是骨骼变硬，然后准备进入第二阶段
All right, Major, we've got to
get it before it hits Stage
好了，上校，我们要在他进入第三阶段前
Three and increases in size
again.
和变大前找到他
Increases in size? What are you talking about?
What does that mean? Who are you guys?
变大？你们在说什么？什么意思？你们是什么人？
Why are you hunting a spider?
为什么要抓一个蜘蛛？
We appreciate your time, Mr.
Mathis. Lieutenant,
感谢你抽出时间，Mathis中尉
will you escort these two
gentlemen off the premises?
你能护送这两位先生走出房屋吗？
No, no, no, no, no, don't brush
me off...
不，别无视我
Hey, it's not going to stay in
the service tunnel very long.
嘿，他不会在工作隧洞里呆太久
You're way out of your league,
son.
这不是你能管的，儿子
All right.
好了
Well, I've had worse job
interviews.
好吧，我有一个很糟的工作面试
I think your boss really likes
me. I thought it went well.
我觉得你的老板很喜欢我，我进行的很不错
He doesn't like games.
他不喜欢游戏
He doesn't like games?
他不喜欢游戏？
Mm-mm.
Then what's with the secrecy?
Just tell us what's going on?
那就告诉我秘密是什么，告诉我们发生了什么
Look, we made a mistake, and now we're taking
care of it, and that's all you need to know.
听着，我们犯了一个错误，而现在我们是来解决麻烦的，这就是你们需要知道的
No, no, no, no, no, what does that mean,
"We made a mistake"? Like "We" made this mistake?
不，我们犯了一个错误指的是什么？就像，我们犯了这个错误？
I've got to get back, so why don't you two
take off before Braxton has you arrested.
我要回去了，所以你们为什么不在Braxton逮捕你们前离开
Wow. Uh, Lieutenant.
哇，中尉
Yes?
怎么了？
Just in case the military or you
should need any assistance at all...
万一军队或者你需要什么帮助的话...
...this is my card.
这是我的名片
Mister...
Alex...
Alex.
小姐
Alex...
Mathis.
On Twitter it's bad-ass bug
killer.
我的微博是坏虫子杀手
If you think of anything else important,
you can give me a call.
如果你发现了什么重要的事,打给我
Oh, so look at that. That wasn't so difficult,
was it? I will definitely be giving you a call.
听着,这并不难,我会解释给你听的
All right. All right.
好的,好的
I appreciate it, and I could
friend you.
我谢谢你,我可以和你做朋友
All right, don't let this get out.
And try to stay out of trouble.
好了,别掉出来了,别惹麻烦
Hm.
Wow
哇
Hm, what a nice lady. I think
she likes you.
多好的一天,我觉得她喜欢你
Can't believe I let this one get
away.
不敢相信我让这个走了
She's right there. I call her.
她在呢,我打给她
No, no, no, no, no, Jose, the
spider?
不,Jose，蜘蛛？
Oh, yeah. Hey, but where are you
going?
是的，嘿，你往哪去？
What do you mean, where am I going? This is it, buddy.
- What?
什么意思，我往哪走？就是这里，兄弟 -什么？
The end of our adventure. It's
been fun.
我们冒险的重点，会很有趣
Hey, you cannot give up now,
Alex.
嘿，现在不能放弃，Alex
You heard her. She's got the Army working with her.
What are we supposed to do?
你听到了，有军人和她在一起，我们还能做什么？
But isn't this, like, the
biggest spider ever?
但不是这样，有史以来最大蜘蛛？
Yes, this is, without question,
the biggest spider on record.
毫无疑问的，有史以来
Yes, so it would be good business, right,
for you to catch it or kill it.
所以这会是笔很好的生意，让你去抓或者杀了它
Yes, if I could catch it or kill
it, which I can't.
是的，如果我能抓住或者杀了他，但是我不行
Okay, but it could make you
famous, right?
你会出名的，好吗？
Yes, this would get a lot of
press. What are you getting at?
这真有压力，你的意思如何？
Look, you could be super-
exterminator.
你会是一个，超级终结者
And Jose. And my boss told me to help you,
so I'm going to help you,
Jose，我的老板要我帮你，所以我会帮你
and you know, like, how? Like
Robin helps the Batman.
你知道吗，就像罗宾帮蝙蝠侠一样
Like Tonto helps the Lone Ranger.
Like Kato helps the Green Hornet.
就像汤头帮助独行侠，卡托帮助青蜂侠
Yeah.
好的
Like Sancho Panza helps Don
Quixote.
像桑丘・潘沙帮助堂吉诃德一样
Yes.
知道了
Like John Oates helps Daryl
Hall, baby.
像John Oates帮助Daryl Hall一样（音乐家）
Yes, we are going to do this.
We are going to show her that spiders don't fly.
我们要这样做，我们要告诉她蜘蛛不会飞
Yes.
是的
And spiders don't swim.
蜘蛛不会游泳
Yes.
是的
Some do, but that's not the point. You and I are
going to find this spider before they do. Come on.
虽然有些会，不过那不是重点，我们要在他们之前找到蜘蛛，快
Let's do it.
行动
Wicked.
真顽皮
The five-mile radius should be enough.
Let's get some eyes out there.
5英里半径应该够了，我们安排人观察一下
Any sign?
有情况吗？
Containment is our priority
right now.
控制现在是我们的第一目标
We have to neutralize the target
before somebody out there sees it.
我们要在有人看到它之前消灭它
The mere sight of this thing
will cause mass panic.
这家伙的一点点动静都会引起恐慌
Sir, we have a problem.
长官，我们有麻烦了
Dodd, who shot the amateur video
Dodd，拍下了可以证明有
claims it was footage of a giant spider
measuring over six feet in length.
六尺长的蜘蛛存在的足迹的影像
We now go live to the scene of
this strange sighting.
I saw a big-ass spider. I came
around the corner.
我看到了一个大屁股蜘蛛，在角落里
- First thing I had to do was get my phone out.
- Ain't nobody gonna believe this...
我拿出电话，但是没人相信这个
I seen this spider was coming at me, man.
It had multip... like, what, eight, six legs?
我看到蜘蛛走向我，他有大概，8,6条腿？
Yeah, about that.
是的
It had multiple legs, dope.
他有很多腿，笨蛋
It had multiple eyes.
他有很多腿
It was multicultured.
而且五彩缤纷的
The fool's on crack!
这疯子昏过头了！
If I see the spider again, I'm
gonna whoop his ass.
如果再让我看到蜘蛛，我会爆他的菊
Are we ready to the spider?
准备去抓蜘蛛了吗？
Yeah!
是的
You better hide your kids,
you better hide your wife 'cause there's a big-ass...
你最好藏起你的孩子，最好藏起你的妻子，因为有一只
bigger than a spi... there's a
mega-spider on the loose.
大屁股蜘蛛，一只巨大的蜘蛛在游荡
Find that building and the
connecting service tunnel.
找到那栋楼和连接隧道
Yes.
是
It is moving into Stage Three.
进入第三阶段了
Thank you, Doctor. Karly.
谢谢，Karly医生
I'm on it.
我准备好了
We're going to need a miracle.
我们需要奇迹
Hey, I like that song, Alex.
我喜欢那首歌，Alex
I like that music, too, my
friend, but we've got to focus.
我也是，朋友，但现在我们需要专心
You're right. Focus. Okay, so
what is the biggest spider ever?
是的，集中，所以什么是有史以来最大的蜘蛛
Biggest spider ever has to be
the Goliath birdeater.
最大的蜘蛛应该是亚马逊食鸟蛛
Yeah, unbelievable.
This thing's got a six-inch abdomen, three-inch fangs,
不敢相信，这家伙有六英寸长的腹部和三英寸长的螯角
13 inches across. But I gotta tell you,
what we're following now...
一共十三英寸，我要告诉你，我们要跟着什么
Yeah.
好的
This thing, what I saw...
我看见的这个家伙...
Yes.
恩
Much bigger.
还要大一些
Oh, come on.
真的吗
I'm not kidding.
不开玩笑
13 1/2 inches?
13.5英尺?
Much bigger.
比这还要大
14 inches. 14 1/2 inches.
14?14.5
Much bigger.
不止
15 inches.
I'll meet you on the other side.
我在那边等你
15 1/2... 16 inches?
15.5...16?
20 inches.
20 inches?
20?
What I saw was 20 inches long
and black.
是一只20英寸又长又黑的
Sounds fun.
真搞笑
Sir, there's a phone call for
you.
长官,您的电话
This is Major Tanner.
我是Tanner上校
Yeah, it's Officer Edwards with
the LAPD.
我是洛杉矶警察局的Edward长官
Something down here you're
probably going to want to see
这里有你想看的东西
What is your location?
你的位置在哪？
So what is this thing?
所以是个什么东西？
It's probably some cross breed
of spider.
可能是某种蜘蛛的杂交种
I don't know. It's just, like,
a gigantic black widow.
不知道，就像一个巨人黑寡妇
Okay, so where would a black
widow go?
好吧，所以黑寡妇在哪？
Well, black widows are night feeders,
so it's going to be looking for easy
黑寡妇是夜行性狩猎者，所以
access outside the sewer
tunnels, some food supply, not a
能再排污管里找到他，提供一些事物
lot of traffic, calm area,
possibly-
别太吵闹，可能
Un ro.
What?
什么？
Un ro. The river.
Yes, yes, the L.A. River.
是的，洛杉矶河
Okay, let's go.
好了，我们走
Let's go.
出发
There. There's something.
有东西在这
Oh, sweet mother of God.
哦，我的慈禧太后啊
It built this under one hour.
在一个小时内造出来的
Looks like it housed maybe 20 or
30 people at night.
看起来他在晚上抓了二三十个人
Do you see any survivors?
你有看到幸存者吗
No. No one left. Except for
maybe some leftovers.
没有，只有些残留物
A little more to the right,
please.
去右边一点
It has molted.
被腐蚀了
Center. Center Command, this is
Major Tanner.
总部，指挥部总部，这里是Tanner上校
We are at Stage Three. I
repeat. We are at Stage Three.
第三阶段了，重复，到达第三阶段
This town has no idea what's
coming.
这个小镇不知道要面对的是什么
Ah, it looks like they beat us
to the punch.
看起来他们抢先一步了
Yeah, but do you think they
killed it?
是的，但你觉得他们杀了它吗？
I don't know. I'm about to find
out.
不知道，我会发现的
Hello?
哈喽？
Hey, it's, uh... it's Alex. I was just wondering, um,
so you got your spider, huh?
嘿，是Alex，我只是猜测，你抓到你的蜘蛛了吗？
What? Where are you?
什么？你在哪？
Where are we?
我们在哪？
We're right across the river
from you...
你和你的部下的
...and your soldiers. Hey.
河对面
Listen, we just missed it.
Anything else?
听着，我们错过了，还有什么吗？
Anything else. Um-
其他，
Ask her out, man.
约她出来
What?
什么？
Ask her out, Alex.
约她出来，Alex
No.
不
Don't be scared.
别害怕
I'm not scared.
我没害怕
Listen. No offense, but I don't have time for this,
all right? Good-bye, Alex.
听着，无意冒犯，但我没时间做这个，好吗？再见Alex
I was wondering if maybe-
我在想是否可以..
What? Hello.
什么?哈喽
What happened?
怎么了
Uh, spider's still on the loose.
蜘蛛还没死
Oh, it is?
是吗?
Yes.
是的
Okay, so. Where do you think it
would go from here?
所以你觉得它会从这去哪?
Well, it's going to be looking
for food and fast.
他会去找食物,很快
Thought you said it hunts at
night.
你说过它会在晚上捕猎
Yeah, but something this size is
going to hunt when it's hungry,
是的,但这种体型的生物只只有在饿的时候才会捕猎
and there's nothing around but
industrial space.
这个工业区什么都没有
It could hide in the hills.
它可以躲在小山上
Yes, it could... Yes, it's going to be looking for
higher ground. Very good guess, Seor Watson.
是的,它可以,它会找一个高高的地方,不错的猜想Watson
It's going to need tree cover.
有树遮掩的地方
You know, my cousin had a
quinceaera at Elysian Park.
你知道，在Elysian公园我叔叔有一颗树
It's Sunday. There's lots of
people there cooking out.
今天是周末，有很多人在那野炊
That's where I would be with my
family if I had the day off-
如果我休假的话我就会和我的家人去那
Hey, you know what? Elysian
Park. Let's try Elysian Park.
嘿，你知道吗？Elysian公园，我们去Elysian公园
Are you serious? I just said
Elysian Park, Alex.
你认真的吗？我只是说说而已
Come on. Vmonos!
就这样决定了
The drone has a lock on our
target, sir.
无人机锁定我们的目标了
Good God.
谢天谢地
Location?
地点？
Elysian Park
Elysian公园
Get units there now.
把部队撤离那里
Oh, stop sign, Alex.
噢，停车标志，Alex
No, there's no slowing down.
We've got to get to the park.
不，我们不能慢下来，我们要去Elysian公园
Oh, there goes the stop sign
我们路过了停车点
We have got to get to the park
and evacuate these people.
我们要去Elysian公园救人
Oh, boy
又来了
Oh, man. We gonna get it now. I
told you to drive slow.
你看吧，我告诉过你减速
I'll do the talking, okay?
我负责谈话，好吗
Yeah, hope so. You're the white
guy.
但愿吧，你是个白人
Alex, wait-Oh, man.
Alex，等下
Listen, I'm a professional
Driver.
听着，我是个职业车手
I'm going to need you to step
back into your vehicle.
我要你回到你的车中
No, no, no, but there's something huge in the park,
and I'm just saying we have a major-
不，有个大东西在公园里，我们有上校的..
Alex, listen to him. Okay? Just
listen to him-
Alex，听他的好吗？听他的..
Excuse me, sir, I need you to
step back inside the car.
不好意思,先生,我需要你回到车里去
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇唔
Put your hands on the dash
board.
把你你的双手放在仪表盘上
Okay, good luck. Good luck,
Alex.
放松,放松,Alex
Back inside the car.
回到车里
I understand what this is all
about.
我知道这是什么
What's going on in the park
today? You got a picnic?
公园里怎么了？野餐？
All right,
maybe I should just donate to the officer's fund. Huh?
好的，我会捐赠警务人员的资金好吗？
Is that right?
好吗？
Huh? Is that what it's going to
take?
这就是会发生的事吗？
Is that... Is that what this is?
是这样的吗？
That's exactly what that is.
就是这样
A donation to the officer's
fund.
警务人员的捐赠基金
Yes, siree. Can I go now?
是的，长官，我能走了吗？
This is a 12... $12 donation.
Seriously, man?
这里有，只有12块，真的吗？
Yeah, this is all I got.
我身家财产了
Twelve dollars? Sir, I'd like
for you to turn around.
12快？转过身
Turn around? I'm a professional.
转身？我是个教授
Put your... Turn around, put your
hands on the car, please.
把你的手..转过去,把你的手放在车上
There are hundreds if not
thousands of people in the park..
没有上千也有上百的人在公园里
Their lives depend on us getting
there. -Is that right?
他们的生命岌岌可危 -真的吗?
Yes, absolutely.
绝对是的
All units, all units, please
report to Elysian Park.
所有单位注意,去Elysian公园
Yeah.
是的
There's a disturbance in
progress.
干扰进展
Okay.
好的
Huh? Huh?
Elysian... Elysian Park?
Oh, look at that. Okay, go! Go!
看着那个，快去！
Don't... Don't be waving me off.
You better get out of here, all right?
别晃我，你最好去那里，好吗？
This works. This works.
这个有用
Can I have my bribe back?
我能拿回我的贿赂物吗？
Hey, what are you doing?
你在做什么？
I'm going to ram it.
撞击它
Oh. What?
什么？
Yes.
是的
No, you're joking.
你在搞笑
Yes!
是的
Go! Go! Go!
快快快！
I'm going as fast as I can.
我要尽快到那
Are you okay? Are you okay?
你还好吗？
No.
不
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
No.
不好
You're not okay?
你不好？
No, I'm not okay.
是的，我不好
Okay.
知道了
Who in the hell is that idiot?
那个白痴是谁
That's Alex Mathis.
Alex Mathis
The exterminator?
杀虫专家？
Yes, sir.
是的
He's going to get himself
killed.
他会害死他自己的
What?
什么？
Okay, listen. Enough of this.
Your Spanglish is pressuring me. All right?
好了，听着，够了 你混有西班牙文英语已经说服我了好吗
I can't go on.
我不能继续
Hello, Western Exterminator. We
care.
哈喽，杀虫先生
Alex, this is Lieutenant Brandt.
Alex，我是Brandt中尉
Hey, Karly, how are you?
We're onto your spider. We're in Elysian Park.
Karly你没事吧？我们去找你的蜘蛛了，在Elysian公园
Listen, we're here, Alex. Get clear.
We're going to handle this.
听着，我们到了，Alex，清醒点，我们要搞定它
Uh, no, no, we're going to take
care of the spider, and then I
不，我们要搞定蜘蛛，然后
am going to take you out to
dinner.
带你去吃晚饭
Alex, I'm not joking. You're
heading right into a crossfire.
Alex，不是开玩笑，你走进死交叉火力里了
I'm sorry. We're heading into a
what?
不好意思，我们走进什么了？
A crossfire.
交叉火力
A crossfire. What's a...
交叉火力，什么..
A crossfire? What's a...
交叉火力?
All right, on my command.
好了,听我命令
Open fire!
开火!
My truck!
我的车!
You son of a bitch!
你个狗娘养的的!
Alex, don't!
Alex，别！
Are you insane? What were you
thinking?
你疯了吗？想什么呢？
Hey, did you miss me?
嘿，想我了吗？
You could've been killed.
你会被杀了的
Well, we just thought we'd bring
the spider to you.
好吧，我们只是觉得我们把蜘蛛带给你了
I don't have time to deal with this clown.
Get him out of my sight.
我没时间跟这个白痴闹，把他带走
Yes, sir.
遵命
You're welcome.
不用谢
Keep him out of our way.
Lieutenant, regroup the men and form a perimeter.
把他带走，中尉，集合你的人拉条封锁线
Yes.
是
I want to kill that bastard
while it's still in the woods.
我想杀了那个混蛋但它一直在树林里
Yes, Major.
是的，长官
And get some more men up here.
带多些人来
Hey, I lost my truck.
嘿，我失去了我的卡车
Uh, I lost my glasses.
噢，我失去了我的眼睛
You will need more firepower.
There's enough explosive in here to take out a tank.
你会需要更多的火力
Thank you.
谢谢
I lost my truck. You're worried
about your glasses?
我没了卡车你还在想你的眼睛？
I'm... yeah, you're right.
我，好吧
Hey, Karly, what about me?
嘿，Karly，我呢？
What about you?
你？
Well, should I come with you?
Jose and I can be our own unit.
我该跟着你吗？Jose和我可是自己人
Yeah, I shot it a whole bunch.
All right, listen, guys.
Seriously I've really appreciated everything
you've done, but we've got it
from here. Okay?
Wait, Karly.
You guys, listen. You guys did a
great job.
Thank you. Karly, you need my
help.
Alex, what I've got to do now is
move out.
You and your men are about to walk into a death trap.
The wooded area's her terrain.
This is home turf advantage for her.
They don't call her one of the greatest
predators on earth for nothing.
Trust me. Karly, you need my help
Alex, this is my job.
How come women never listen to
me?
What?
Stay sharp, boys.
Now, if you come across a hide or lair,
your first priority is to drop the thermite pack
and fall back immediately.
All detonation will be signaled from here.
Look out. Look out!
Where's Balzda? Where's Balzda?
We lost all of Alpha company.
Lon's camera's down, too, sir.
Target acquired. Target
acquired.
Engage.
Sir, we lost Private Parker.
Send teams Delta, Echo, Foxtrot
now.
Damn. Guys, I'm stuck.
Yeah, well, I'm stuck in this
stuff, too.
Okay, it's... Charlie One. It's... Charlie One.
We need immediate backup now.
Lieutenant Brandt.
Yes, sir.
If it gets in your vicinity...
...and you have a chance to end
this, are you prepared to do so?
Yes, sir.
Shh-shh-shh-shh-shh-shh. Quiet.
Quiet
Hi. What are you doing here?
I'm saving your ass. What do you
think I'm doing here?
Be careful. Be careful.
I know. I know.
Oh, my God.
Come on, hurry, hurry. Get me
out. Get me out.
I am. I am
If I just heat the knife,
we should be able to cut right through it. Hold still.
Here... Here we go.
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
Oh, yeah, yeah, of course.
Okay, we've got to keep moving.
And don't stop moving.
Okay.
Okay... whoa, whoa, whoa, keep
moving. Smooth, smooth, smooth.
Okay, I have a contingency plan.
Yeah, what's that?
You see this pack on my back?
Yeah?
Yeah.
It's filled with explosives that'll
blow that thing a mile high.
That's not good! If you blow that thing a mile high,
you're going to blow us a mile high.
I'm sorry, Alex.
What? Are you kidding me?
The girl of my dreams wanna kill me on my day off?
This is great. Please don't do
it!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Come one. We gotta go. Let's get
out-
Come on. Come on!
Come on, Karly!
I'm coming.
Karly!
No!
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, guys. Sorry, Alex.
Sorry, Alex? What do you mean, sorry Alex?
What's the plan, guys? We gotta rescue her.
You're kidding, Alex.
Kidding? No, I'm not kidding.
She's as good as dead. Let's
move on.
No! Wh-What are we all?
We're just numbers to you guys? Is that it?
Hey, Braxton, come on. What is this?
It's just collateral damage?
Lieutenant Brandt and I went
through hell and back to get her,
so don't tell me about losing a
friend.
She was a good soldier, and her
death will not be in vain.
Now, we're running out of time.
It's still out there.
And about to run amok into Stage
Five.
St... Okay. What-What's Stage
Five?
Doc, what happens in Stage Five?
Come on.
This is not the first time you
guys have dealt with this.
What did you make that is
running around killing people?
We didn't make anything, at
least not intentionally.
This arachnid is an aberration
from several unusual technologies.
Come on. In layman's terms, what
are we dealing with?
Alien biology, not terrestrial.
So you're saying the spider's an
alien?
Yeah.
Not exactly, but yes. DNA cross breeding
from microbial fossil found in Martian soil.
So you made a spider do it with
an alien. That's messed up.
No, no, no.
That's messed up, guys. This is
your people, Alex.
No, no, no, we did cross breed
two species.
We isolated separate genes, one
of which, in particular,
produces a superior growth hormone.
It's promise is infinite.
Giant tomatoes to feed the whole
world and such.
"Tomatoes" is the first word I
understood. You know?
But something went wrong.
No kidding.
I got a question for you.
Yes.
So why do we got the giant spider?
I don't get it. You get it?
I don't get it. What's with the
spider, doc?
We don't get it. You get it,
Braxton?
It was an accident. One of the
fruit plants that were brought
in as a test subject had a spider's nest hidden inside.
The arachnid biology...
...was immediately responsive to
our growth hormone.
Major and I monitored four
stages of growth.
Letting it proceed to Stage
Five was deemed unacceptable.
What happens in Stage Five?
Reproduction.
Of course. Reproduction. I should've guessed that.
Yes, of course reproduction.
It would have to be
reproduction, right?
Because this fairytale has got
spiders from Mars, right?
It's a nice little bedtime story
to tell us you're telling us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got spiders humping each
other.
Alex, even with our high-tech equipment,
you managed to find it the same time we did.
Yes, I did.
No, wait. We did. Okay?
Right.
Correct?
You seem to understand its
nature.
Yes, I do.
So what's your best guess?
Oh, so now you want our help,
huh? School them, Alex.
All right,
my professional opinion is that without question,
she's going to lay her eggs as far away
from a populated area as she can get.
Humans she doesn't trust. She
never has.
So you're not going to find her
anywhere near a populated area.
What, like under a bridge or a
warehouse or s...
No, no, even more isolated. Far
away.
Sir, sir.
Far away.
Sir, I think you need to see
this.
We have a live feed of
Newscopter 8 that has spotted...
...the creature headed toward
Little Tokyo.
We advise you that if you are in
that area to evacuate immediately.
Or she might go downtown.
Oh, l-look. It's right there.
Found her.
It's big.
It appears to be climbing up the
top of City Hall.
The size of it is just unbelievable.
It also appears to be hostile.
If you are in the downtown
area...
All right, son, this is Tanner.
Request status on Operation Ground Swell.
Call in an air strike, Major.
Wait. Air strike? What air
strike?
Contingency.
You can't just drop a bomb here.
Oh, that's not good.
No, you can't... you can't bomb
downtown L.A.
We're running a little low on options,
so I'm calling in a targeted air strike.
You're risking the lives of
thousands of people.
Saving millions.
Wait a minute. There's got to be
a better way
Enough of this. Remove this
Western terminator.
What?
Oh, yeah? I'd like to see you
try it, pretty guy.
Oh, Okay. You got it.
Okay, we're leaving.
Sir, we have a lock on the
building.
Zooming in.
Is that Lieutenant Brandt?
I need a minute.
Copy that.
I hope you have insurance.
The company has insurance, yes.
Well, don't worry about it-
Alex, wait. It's Karly. She's
still alive.
Don't mess with me.
That spider,
she laid her eggs on top of the Epic Bank Building.
There are a lot of people trapped up there.
Karly's one of them.
Okay, so what do we do?
Well, you have about 24 minutes
before the jets arrive there.
And what happens before then is
up to you.
I'll drive.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Okay, so what's the plan, Alex?
Stop the spider, save
the city, kiss the girl.
Oh, good. Any idea how to do
that?
No
That's what I thought.
Our guns are doing nothing
against this thing.
Disengage. Disengage. Pull back,
but maintain visual contact.
See, it's a perfect target up there.
If we can take it out on the rooftop,
it'll keep civilian casualties
to a minimum
As long as we take out that
building before the eggs hatch.
So can I ask you something else,
Alex?
Sure. Go, Mexican Robin.
How are we going to kill this
big spider?
I'm trying to figure that one
out. I mean, we can't shoot it.
Why?
Why? Because it's huge.
The exoskeleton alone is stronger than anything
we've got to penetrate it, and it's resistant to flames.
It's resistant to any kind of heat.
We have not even created a fire
suit strong enough to-
Fire, eh? How about fuego?
No, no, I just said it's
resistant to fire.
Yes, but the web catches on
fire, so can we use that?
Wait a minute.
What?
Wait a minute. That's it. Jose!
If we can ignite the spinneret,
we can blow it up from the inside out.
Really?
Yes!
What's a spinneret?
Spinnerets.
Spin.
Er...
er...
...ets.
Spinnerets.
Where's the spinnerets?
In its ass.
So we have to shoot the spider
in the butt.
In the butt.
How we going to do that?
That's right.
Uh, how we going to do that?
With this.
Oh, baby.
Right?
Wicked.
Where's the air strike?
E.T.A. two minutes.
Have them circle once more.
You are insane, Braxton. You can't risk these
eggs hatching. Take down that building now.
I'm done with you scientists.
You started this thing.
Now, you let us finish it.
Remove this man.
Escort him out of my command
center now.
I will see you in hell, Braxton.
Get me Alex on the phone.
Western. We live to kill.
Alex, you have 10 minutes to get
to the 60th floor.
After that I have no choice.
We can't risk any of those eggs hatching.
Ten minutes is all we're going
to need.
Look out. Look out!
No, no.
Jose! Hey, Jose!
Okay, I've got to go save Karly.
I've got to go save those people.
I'm coming with you.
No, we may not get out of there
in time.
Then we better get moving. Let's
do it, Alex.
Air strike E.T.A. five minutes
away.
E.T.A. three minutes.
God help us all.
We're gonna kill some spiders.
Gonna kill some spiders dead.
We're gonna kills some spiders.
Gonna shoot those muthas in the head.
And stop.
That's pretty good.
That was all right.
Let's do this. You ready?
I'm ready.
You nervous?
Yes.
It's good that you're nervous.
Let's do this.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no.
This is what I was afraid of. She's laid her eggs.
Holy juevos.
Oh, look at this.
Oh, man.
Alex!
Karly.
She's alive.
You were right.
I'm going to go help her. You
help these people.
Okay, I will.
There you go. Go towards the exit on the left,
there's a lot of spiders on the right. Okay
Alex!
Okay, I'm right here. Right
here.
Just promise me this is the last time that
I'm going to have to rescue you today.
I mean, seriously, two saves in
one day
Hurry.
Alex! Alex!
I got it.
Nice
Oh, boy
Here they come. Time to go!
Help me! Oh, my God, help me!
I need a hand. I need a hand!
Oh, my God, she's dead.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
Alex!
Come on, Alex! Clear out! Clear
out!
Come on, Alex!
Thank you for calling Western.
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come
on! Come on! Come on!
Nice shot.
Yeah, well, now we're even
No, not quite
What?
We're out of time.
Engage target. Engage target.
Yes!
Well, let's not celebrate just
yet.
So how much you gonna charge for
killing the big spider?
I don't know, but I hope it
covers the cost of a new truck.
Yes, he is. The major wants to
talk to you.
Major? Hope I'm not in trouble.
I hope not either.
Yeah, Major?
I gotta hand it to you, kid. You knocked it
out of the park. Thank you for saving Karly.
Well, thank you very much, sir.
I told you I'm a professional.
That you are, son. That you are.
Yeah, well, any time you have any trouble,
you know who to call,
except it's not going to be
cheap. I've got a partner now.
And there's a little business about my,
uh... my truck. I made some modifications to it.
Alex.
And I'm not sure that the insurance
at the company's going to cover it.
Alex.
Major, I'm going to have to call
you back.
Alex, can we get out of here?
I'm sorry, Jose. I live to kill.
Okay.
I got your back, babe.
Hey, Jose.
What?
You remember that conversation
we had in the... in the truck?
Which one?
The one about the spinneret.
We're going to shoot it in the
butt.
Find me that bazooka!
You got it, Alex.
You want some of the Ex?
Alex! I'm coming.
Throw it to me.
Watch out, Alex! Wake up, Alex!
Up yours.
Yeah!
Nicely done.
I told you I'm a pro. I'm a pro.
Oh, look at you, you're gross.
Oh.
You've got web all over you.
You're one to talk.
Well, it looks like we're stuck
together for a while.
Is that a problem?
No, I don't have a problem with
that.
Well, what should you do with
the rest of your day off?
I can think of a few things.
All right, you guys.
Okay. Hey, come on, guys. Get a
room. Okay?
Alex, I'm afraid we have a little problem.
What's the biggest cockroach you ever saw?